Inventory of the Kenneth Holland papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches by KH, 1955-1967 (Box 55:)
  - 1965 (Folder 55: 22-24)
  - 1966 (Folder 55: 25)
  - 1967 (Folder 55: 26)
- Article by KH, 1937 (Folder 56: 1)
- Study of Civilian Conservation Corps, 1941 (Folder 56: 2-3)
- Report on USAID activities in Venezuela, 1968 (Folder 56: 4-5)
- Speeches by KH, 1962-1969 (Box 56)
  - 1962 (Folder 56: 6)
  - 1969 (Folder 56: 7)
- Correspondence and memoranda, 1941-1956 (Folder 56: 8)
- Latin American universities, 1967 (Folder 57: 1)
- Articles by KH, 1936-1941 (Folder 57: 2)
- Study of Civilian Conservation Corps, 1941 (Folder 57: 3)
- Brandeis University, 1968 (Folder 57: 4)
- Correspondence, 1928-1975 (Folder 57: 5)
- Notes, 1928-1932 (Folder 57: 6)
- Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1975-1976 (Folder 58: 1-2)
- Conference on Higher Education in the American Republics, 1973 (Folder 58: 3)
- Fletcher-Keio program, 1975 (Folder 58: 4)
- IIE reports, 1933 (Folder 58: 5)
- KH's editorship of Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, 1975 (Folder 58: 6)
- Council on Foreign Relations, 1977 (Folder 58: 7)
- Correspondence, 1948-1976 (Folder 58: 8)
- Articles by KH, 1931-1971 (Folder 58: 9)
- Speech by KH, 1977 (Folder 58: 10)
- Notes, 1970 (Folder 58: 11)
- UNESCO materials, 1949-1950 (Box 59:)
  - Speech by KH, 1949 (Folder 59: 1)
  - Reconstruction, 1950 (Folder 59: 2)
  - Cultural activities, 1949-1950 (Folder 59: 3)
  - Education, 1949-1950 (Folder 59: 4)
  - Telegrams sent by American embassy in Paris, 1950 (Folder 59: 5)
- Articles by KH, 1941-1977 (Folder 59: 6)
- Notes for articles, 1974-1975 (Folder 59: 7)
- History of the IIE, 1955-1963 (Folder 59: 8)
- Student papers and reading notes, 1928-1932 (Folder 59: 9)
- Printed matter relating to the Civilian Conservation Corps, 1938 (Folder 60: 1-2)
- Printed matter relating to education, 1965-1972 (Folder 60: 3-6)
- Article by KH, 1944 (Folder 60: 7)
- Panama Canal, 1976-1977 (Folder 60: 8)
- Photographs, 1950-1968 (Folder 61: 1)
- Clippings, 1956-1969 (Folder 61: 2)
- Commencement address and speeches by KH, 1965-1974 (Folder 61: 3)
- Articles by KH, 1964-1968 (Folder 61: 4)
- Programs and report, 1964-1969 (Folder 61: 5)
- Correspondence and memoranda, 1945-1976 (Folder 61: 6)
- Printed matter relating to the Civilian Conservation Corps and European youth labor camps, 1939-1942 (Folder 61: 7-8)
- Printed matter relating to education, 1944-1976 (Folder 61: 9-10)
- Notes for research paper on France and problems of security, 1933 (Folder 62: 1-8)
- Scrapbook of clippings and photographs, 1941-1947 (Folder 63: 1)